In the previous video,
在上一个视频中
you saw the logistic regression model.
你看到的是逻辑回归的模型
To train the parameters W and B of the logistic regression model,
为了训练逻辑回归模型的参数w以及b
you need to define a cost function.
你需要定义一个代价函数(cost function)
Let's take a look at the cost function you can use to train logistic regression.
让我们来看一下这个可以用来训练逻辑回归的代价函数
To recap, this is what we had to find from the previous slide.
总的来说 这就是我们从上一张幻灯片中要找的函数
So your output y-hat is sigmoid of w transpose x plus b
所以你的输出y^=sigmoid(wT+b)
where a sigmoid of Z is as defined here.
就像这里定义为sigmoid(z)
So to learn parameters for your model you're given
为了让你的模型来通过学习调整参数
a training set of m training examples and it
你需要给予一个m个样本的训练集
seems natural that you want to find parameters W
这似乎会让你想要在训练集上找到参数w和b
and B so that at least on the training set, the outputs you have.
来得到你的输出
The predictions you have on the training set,
你对训练集的预测值
which we only write as y-hat (i) that that will be close to
我们将它写成y^ 我们希望它会接近于
the ground truth labels y^(i) that you got in the training set.
在训练集中得到的y值
So to throw in a little bit more detail for the equation on top,
所以 为了让上面的方程式更详细一些
we had said that y-hat is as defined at the top for
我们需要说明上面这里定义的y^是对一个训练样本x来说的
a training example x and of course for each training example,
这种形式当然也适用对于每个训练样本
we're using these superscripts with
我们在使用这些带有圆括号的上标
round brackets with parentheses to index and to differentiate examples.
来作索引以及区分样本
Your prediction on training sample (i) which is y-hat (i) is going to
你的训练样本(i)所对应的预测值是y^(i)
be obtained by taking the sigmoid function and applying it to W transpose X,
是用训练样本的wT*x(i)+b然后通过sigmoid函数中得到的
(i) the input that the training example plus B and you can also define Z (i) as follows.
然后你可以把Z定义成这样
Z (i) is equal to the W transpose x (i) plus b.
Z(i)等于wT*x(i)+b
So throughout this course,
所以在这门课里
we're going to use this notational convention,
我们将使用这个符号注解
that the superscript parentheses i refers to data.
就是这个上标(i)来指明数据
X or Y or Z or something else associated with the i-th training example,
表示X或者Y或者Z或者其它数据的第i个训练样本
associated with the i-th example.
所以用第i个样本来表示
That's what the superscript i in parentheses means.
这就是上标(i)的含义
Now, let's see what loss function or error
现在让我们来看看损失函数(loss function)
或叫做误差函数（error function）
function we can use to measure how well our algorithm is doing.
它们可以用来衡量算法的运行情况
One thing you could do is define
the loss when your algorithm outputs
你需要做的第一件事就是定义损失（loss）为
y-hat and the true label as Y to
be maybe the square error or one half a square error.
y^和y的平方差 或者它们平方差的一半
It turns out that you could do this,
结果表明你可以这样做
but in logistic regression people don't usually do
但是通常在逻辑回归中大家都不这么做
this because when you come to learn the parameters,
这是因为当你学习这些参数的时候
you find that the optimization problem which we talk about later becomes non-convex.
你会发现我们后来讨论的优化目标变成非凸的
So you end up with optimization problem with multiple local optima.
你最后会得到很多个局部最优值
So gradient descent may not find the global optimum.
所以梯度下降可能不会找到全局最优值
If you didn't understand the last couple of comments.
如果你不知道最后这几句话
Don't worry about it, we'll get to it in later video.
别担心 我们会在后面的视频中讲到它
But the intuition to take away is that
但是这个的直观理解就是
this function L called the loss function is a function you'll
我们通过这个称为L的损失函数
need to define to measure how good our
output y-hat is when the true label is y.
来衡量你的预测输出值y^和y的实际值有多接近
As square error seems like it might be a reasonable choice
平方误差看起来似乎是一个合理的选择
except that it makes gradient descent not work well.
但是在这里它不能使梯度下降很好地工作
So in logistic regression, we will actually define
所以在逻辑回归中我们实际上将会定义
a different loss function that
plays a similar role as squared error,
一个不同的损失函数 它起着与平方误差相似的作用
that will give us an optimization problem that is
这些会给我们一个凸的优化目标
convex and so we'll see in that later video becomes much easier to optimize.
因此我们将会在后面的视频中看到它变得很容易优化
So, what we use in logistic regression is actually
我们在逻辑回归中所用的实际就是
the following loss function which I'm just like right up here,
我这里指的损失函数
is negative y log y-hat plus one minus y log,
它是一个-(y*log(y^) + (1-y)log(1-y^))
one minus y-hat.
Here's some intuition for why this loss function makes sense.
这里有一些直观理解 为什么这个损失函数能够起作用
Keep in mind that if we're using
记得如果我们使用
squared error then you want the squared error to be as small as possible.
平方误差时你会想要让这个误差尽可能地小
And with this logistic regression loss function,
那么对于这个逻辑回归损失函数
we'll also want this to be as small as possible.
我们同样也想让它尽可能地小
To understand why this makes sense,
为了更好地理解为什么它能够起作用
let's look at the two cases.
让我们来看两个例子
In the first case,
在第一个例子中
let's say Y is equal to one then the loss
我们说y等于1时
function y-hat comma y is justice for us to write this negative sign.
损失函数(y^,y)就相当于这里的-ylog(y^)
So this negative log y-hat.
就是-log(y^)
If y is equal to one. Because if y equals
如果y等于1
one then the second term one minus Y is equal to zero.
那么这第二项这里的1-y就等于0
So this says if y equals one you want
negative log y-hat to be as big（little） as possible.
这就是说当y等于1时 你想要把-log(y^)变得尽可能的小（口误）
So that means you want log y-hat to be large,
这意味着你想要把log(y^)变得尽可能的大
to be as big as possible and that means you want y-hat to be large.
这样就意味着你想要y^变得很大
But because y-hat is you know,
但是因为y^是上面所写的
the sigmoid function, it can never be bigger than one.
sigmoid函数 它永远不会比1大
So this is saying that if y is equal to one you,
所以这也就是说如果y等于1时
want y-hat to be as big as possible.
你会想让y^变得尽可能地大
But it can't ever be bigger than one so saying you want y-hat to be close to one as well.
但它永远不会大于1 所以说你要让y^接近1
The other case is if y equals zero.
另一个一个例子就是如果y等于0
If y equals zero then this first term
in the loss function is equal to zero because
如果y等于0 那么损失函数的第一项等于0
y zero and then the second term defines the loss function.
因为y是0 然后第二项就是这个损失函数
So the loss becomes negative log one minus y-hat.
所以这损失函数变成-log(1-y^)
And so if in your learning procedure you try to make the loss function small,
如果在学习过程中你试图让损失函数小一些
what this means is that you want log one minus y-hat to be large.
也就意味着你想要log(1-y^)变得很大
And because it's a negative sign there and
因为这里是一个负号
then through a similar piece of reason you can conclude
然后通过这一系列类似的理论你可以得出结论
that this loss function is trying to make y-hat as small as possible.
就是这个损失函数正在让y^尽可能的小
And again because y-hat has to be between zero and one.
再者 因为y^只能位于0到1之间
This is saying that if y is equal to zero then
这就是说y等于0时
your loss function will push the parameters to make y-hat as close to zero as possible.
你的损失函数会让这些参数让y^尽可能地接近于0
Now, there are a lot of functions with roughly this effect that if y is equal
在这门课里会有许多的函数的效果和现在这个类似 就是如果y等于1
to one we try to make y-hat large and if Y is equal to zero we try to make y-hat small.
我们就尽可能让y^变大 如果y等于0 我们尽可能让y^变小
We just gave here in green
我们这里用绿色来写
a somewhat informal justification for this loss function? we'll provide
关于为什么用这个损失函数 我们稍后将会提供一个
an optional video later to give a more formal justification for
可选择性观看的视频 来给出一个更正式的理由
why in logistic regression we like to use the loss function with this particular form.
解释为什么在逻辑回归中我们喜欢使用这种特殊形式的损失函数
Finally, the loss function was defined with respect to a single training example.
最后 损失函数是在单个训练样本中定义的
It measures how well you're doing on a single training example.
它衡量的是你在单个训练样本上的表现如何
I'm now going to define something called the cost function,
现在我要定义一个代价函数(cost function)
which measures how well you're doing an entire training set.
它衡量的是你在全部训练样本上的表现如何
So the cost function J which is applied to
所以这个代价函数J
your parameters W and B is going to be the average with one of
根据之前得到的两个参数w和b J(w, b)等于
the m of the sum of the loss function applied to each of the training examples and turn.
1/m乘以L(y^(i), y(i))的求和
While here y-hat is of course
而y^是
the prediction output by your logistic regression algorithm using you know,
通过逻辑回归算法 用一组特定的参数w和b
a particular set of parameters W and B.
得出的预测输出值
And so just to expand this out,
所以把这个展开
this is equal to negative one over
这等于-1/m
m sum from i equals one through m of the definition of the loss function.
从i=1到m对损失函数的求和
So this is y (i) Log y-hat
这是y(i)*log(y^(i))
(i) plus minus is y (i) log one minus y-hat (i).
+ (1 - y(i))*log(1 - y^(i))
I guess I could put square brackets here.
我想我可以在这里画上方括号
So the minus sign is outside everything else.
负号在外面
So the terminology I'm going to use is that
这里我要用的术语是
the loss function is applied to just a single training example like so.
损失函数只适用于像这样的单个训练样本
And the cost function is the cost of your parameters.
这个代价函数是你参数的总代价
So in training your logistic regression model,
所以在训练你的逻辑回归模型时
we're going to try to find parameters W and B that
我们试图找到合适的参数w和b
minimize the overall cost function J written at the bottom.
来将屏幕下方写的代价函数J的总代价降到最低
So, you've just seen the set up for the logistic regression algorithm,
所以你们刚刚看到了逻辑回归算法的推导
the loss function for training example and the
以及针对单个训练样本的损失函数
overall cost function for the parameters of your algorithm.
和针对你算法所选用参数的总代价函数
It turns out that logistic regression can be viewed as a very very small neural network.
结果表明逻辑回归可以被看作是一个非常小的神经网络
In the next video we'll go over that so you can start
在下一个视频里 我们将会提到
gaining intuition about what neural networks do.
关于神经网络能做什么的直观理解
So that let's go onto the next video about how to
下面我们来看下一段视频
view logistic regression as a very small neural network.
关于如何将逻辑回归看作一个非常小的神经网络